U.S. National Mediation Board Agreements 5806
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Company + The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway, 1931-1974 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- General Grievance Committee + The New York Central Railroad Co. + The Western Pacific Railroad Co., 1929-1946 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Various Agreements (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Various Agreements (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Various Agreements (Box 76, Folder 18)
- The Pennsylvania Railroad Co. + Penn Central Transportation Company, 1965-1970 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Co. + The Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1939-1973 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- The Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway Company + The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Co. + The Boston and Albany Railroad, 1934- 1949 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen + Trainmen and Yardmen, 1938-1954 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railway Co., 1947-1953 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- DM and IR Railway Co. The President of the Emergency, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen + Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen + Brotherhood of Locomotive Trainmen, 1936-1938 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- BRT + Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen + Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, 1946-1963 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers etc. + Spokane Railroad Companies, 1944-1957 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees + Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of American + The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1950-1964 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- 'W' Railroad Companies + 'C' Railroad Companies + Illinois Railroad Companies, 1946-1956 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Various Agreements, 1947-1956 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- New York Railroad Companies, 1924-1957 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co. + The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1970-1974 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. + Port Terminal Railroad Association + Central of Georgia, 1968-1977 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Missouri Railroad Companies, 1942-1975 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, + Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees + Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1942- 1958 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railway Airline and Steamship Clerks + The Order of Railroad Telegraphers + Brotherhood iof Railroad Signalmen of America, 1925- 1974 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Firemen and Enginemen + The Order of Railroad Telegraphers + Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1955-1966 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, 1940-1955 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Maintenance of Way Employees + Firemen, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- New York, 'G' Railway Companies, 1942-1944 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Yardmasters, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Various Railway Companies, 1910-1949 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers + Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen + Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1910-1944 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, + Maintenance of Way Employees, 1972-1978 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks + Maintenance of Way Employees, 1972-1978 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1948-1973 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Conductors, Trainmen, Yardmen, 1927-1956 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Conductors + BRT + Engineers, 1940-1965 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, 1955-1972 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, 1942-1958 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Macon, Dublin and Savannah Railroad Co. + Louisville and Nashville RR + Missouri Pacific RR + The Nashville Chattanooga and St. Louis RR, 1948-1950 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway Co. + Maintenance of Way Employees, 1938-1955 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Railroad Companies 'N', 1926-1953 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Firemen and Engineers, 1923-1955 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Erie, Railroad + Elgin Joliet and Einstein Railway Co. + Burlington Lines, 1951-1968 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Order of Railroad Telegraphers + Chicago Railway Cos., 1922-1950 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers + Chicago RR Companies + The Denver and Rio Grande Western RR Co., 1922-1972 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Maintenance of Way + Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1954-1957 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- The Order of Railroad Telegraphers + Enginemen + Conductors, 1912-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen + American train Dispatchers, 1927-1950 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1963-1973 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Firemen + Engineermen + Enginemen, 1923-1955 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Trainmen + Yardmen + Yardmasters, 1924-1956 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- 'M' Railroad Companies + American Railway Supervisors Associations, 1944 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- BRT + Chicago South Shore and South Bend Railroad, 1938-1948 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Railway Carmen of America + Maintenance of Way Employees, 1934-1967 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Firemen, 1910-1951 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, 1970-1980 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Various Agreements, 1942-1946 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Handship Clerks, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Various Agreements, 1941-1951 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Various Agreements, 1932-1953 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Various Agreements, 1945-1950 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Various Agreements, 1946-1968 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- BRT + Yardmasters, 1944-1951 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Hustlers, Firemen + Conductors, 1922-1945 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- 'S' Railway Companies, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Various Agreements, 1941-1949 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Order of telegraphers + Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company + Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1941-1943 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Various Agreements, 1937-1970 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Various Agreements, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Various Agreements, 1936-1943 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Various Agreements, 1945-1970 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Jacksonville Terminal Company + Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1930-1949 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Various Agreements, 1935 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Various Agreements, 1954-1968 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Various Agreements, 1977-1992 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Various Agreements, 1949-1977 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Various Agreements, 1937-1971 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Various Agreements, 1937-1956 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Denver and Rio Grande Western RR + Chicago Rock Island and Pacific RR Companies, 1955-1984 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Various Agreements, 1941-1945 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Various Agreements, 1951-1957 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Various Agreements, 1951 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Various Agreements, 1940-1962 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Various Agreements, 1935-1958 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Kentucky and Indiana Terminal RR Co. + Boston and Maine RR Co., 1953 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- American Dispatchers Association + Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1938-1976 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- 'B' Railroad Companies + Missouri Pacific Lines, 1952-1955 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Various Agreements, 1921-1957 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Firemen, Engineers, Enginemen + Yardmasters, 1950-1962 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. + United Transportation Union, 1948-1968 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Penn Central Transportation Company + Gulf, Colorado and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1932-1970 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Various Agreements, 1946-1956 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Various Agreements, 1928-1954 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio RR Co. + The Baltimore and Ohio RR Co. + Atlantic Coast Line RR Co., 1951-1974 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Various Agreements, 1937-1944 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Various Agreements, 1939-1941 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Various Agreements, 1941-1949 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Various Agreements, 1956-1978 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Various Agreements, 1929-1959 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Various Agreements, 1926-1959 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Various Agreements, 1954-1979 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Various Agreements, 1951-1973 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Various Agreements, 1937-1941 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- 'S' 'T' 'N' Railroad Companies, 1922-1946 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- The Western Pacific Railroad Co. + The Long Island RR Co. +, 1942-1949 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Chicago RR Companies + Western Maryland Railway Co., 1951-1967 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Co. + Louisville and Nashville RR Co., 1949-1977 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Various Agreements, 1937-1948 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Various Agreements, 1943-1983 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Various Agreements, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Various Agreements, 1923-1951 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Various Agreements, 1940-1972 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Various Agreements, 1947-1974 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Various Agreements, 1945-1971 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Various Agreements, 1937-1968 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Various Agreements, 1926-1957 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Long Island RR Co. + AmTrak, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. + Boston and Albany RR + Missouri Pacific RR Co., 1945-1972 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Various Agreements, 1924-1959 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Various Agreements, 1940-1956 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Various Agreements, 1945-1969 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Various Agreements, 1923-1970 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Various Agreements, 1951-1965 (Box 85, Folder 15)